Guide to the Daniel Finch, Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Letters to Edward Southwell (1671-1730) and others
1702-1704
OSBORN C205
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
0.08
(1 volume)
Nottingham and Winchilsea, Daniel Finch, Earl of, 1647-1730
Immediate Source of Acquisition
For provenance information, consult the appropriate curator.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The following finding aid is a complete inventory of the contents of Osborn c205. This list was reformatted from previously existing cataloging.
- Osborn c205
  - BLATHWAYT, WILLIAM, 1649-1717
    - 2 ALS to Edward Southwell (1671-1730), 1703 (Box 1)
      Scope and Contents
      1703 Aug 3 and 7
      Whitehall
      4 p.; 23 x 18 cm.
      205/10,37
  - NORTHEY, SIR EDWARD, 1652-1723
    - ALS [copy] to Daniel Finch, earl of Nottingham and Winchilsea (1647-1730), 1703 Aug 7 (Box 1)
      London
      2 p.; 23 x 18 cm.
      205/11
  - NOTTINGHAM AND WINCHILSEA, DANIEL FINCH, EARL OF, 1647-1730
    - 3 ALS to William Blathwayt (1649-1717), 1702-03 (Box 1)
      3 p.; 22 x 18 cm.
      205/1,2,14
  - NOTTINGHAM AND WINCHILSEA, DANIEL FINCH, EARL OF, 1647-1730
    - 25 ALS and LS to Edward Southwell (1671-1717), 1703 (Box 1)
      30 p.; 22 x 18 cm.
      205/ 3,4,7-9,12,13,16-34
  - NOTTINGHAM AND WINCHILSEA, DANIEL FINCH, EARL OF, 1647-1730
    - ALS to Sidney Godolphin, 1st Earl of Godolphin (1645-1712), 1704 Apr 17 (Box 1)
      1 p.; 22 x 18 cm.
      205/35
  - STANHOPE, JAMES STANHOPE, 1ST EARL, 1673-1721
    - Letter (extract) to Sir Charles Hedges (1650-1714), 1703 Jul 9 (Box 1)
      [The Hague]
      2 p.; 22 x 18 cm.
      With copy extract from anonymous
      letter dated from Amsterdam.
      205/5-6
  - VANHOMRIGH, BARTHOLOMEW, D. 1703
    - 3 ALS to Edward Southwell (1671-1730), 1703 Aug (Box 1)
      Dublin
      6 p.; 23 x 18 cm.
      205/15,37,39
  - VANHOMRIGH, BARTHOLOMEW, D. 1703
    - ALS to the Commissioners of Transportation, 1703 Aug 8 (Box 1)
      2 p.; 23 x 17 cm.
      Accompanied by "A list of transport
      ships engaged and hired by Br.
      Vanhomrigh for transporting 1500
      men from Ireland to Portugal".
      205/38